{"weather":[{"level":"1","type":"weather","question":"I fall from the sky, but I'm not a bird. I make puddles. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💧I am wet."},{"text":"☔️ You need an umbrella when I fall."},{"text":"🌧️ Plants like me."}],"options":[{"label":"Rain","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sun","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Stars","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"2","type":"weather","question":"I am big and yellow and hot. I shine in the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"☀️I make you feel warm."},{"text":"😎 You need sunglasses when I'm out."},{"text":"🌻Flowers love me."}],"options":[{"label":"The Moon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The Sun","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Cloud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"3","type":"weather","question":"I am white and fluffy. I float in the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐑 I look like a sheep."},{"text":"🌬️ The wind helps me move."},{"text":"☁️ Sometimes I bring rain."}],"options":[{"label":"A Star","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Cloud","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Leaf","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"4","type":"weather","question":"I am cold and white. I fall in winter. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧤You need gloves to play with me."},{"text":"❄️ I melt when it's warm."},{"text":"☃️ You can make a snowman with me."}],"options":[{"label":"Snow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sand","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Grass","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"5","type":"weather","question":"I blow through the trees. Sometimes I'm gentle, sometimes I'm strong. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍃 I can make leaves fall."},{"text":"🪁 You can fly a kite with me."},{"text":"🌬️ I am air moving fast."}],"options":[{"label":"The Rain","isCorrect":false},{"label":"The Wind","isCorrect":true},{"label":"The Fire","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"6","type":"weather","question":"I light up the sky with a crash and a boom. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"⚡I come with rain."},{"text":"🌩️ I am very loud."},{"text":"😳 You might be scared of me."}],"options":[{"label":"Lightning","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sunshine","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A rainbow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"7","type":"weather","question":"I appear after the rain, with many colors. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌈 I have red, yellow and blue."},{"text":"☀️ I need the sun and rain to appear."},{"text":"✨ Some people think there's gold at my end."}],"options":[{"label":"A Star","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Rainbow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Cloud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"8","type":"weather","question":"I am frozen rain. I can hurt if I hit you. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧊 I am made of ice."},{"text":"🤕 Be careful; I can make bumps."},{"text":"🌧️ I fall from the sky like rain, but I'm hard."}],"options":[{"label":"Hail","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Dew","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"9","type":"weather","question":"I am a white fog, that can limit visibility outside. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌫️ Sometimes I cover the mountains."},{"text":"🚗 You have to drive slow, when I'm around."},{"text":"☁️ I am like a low cloud on the ground."}],"options":[{"label":"Snowdrift","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Tornado","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fog","isCorrect":true}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"10","type":"weather","question":"I'm hot air that rises and spins around very fast, destroying everything in my path. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌪️ I look like a big funnel."},{"text":"🏠 I can lift houses up."},{"text":"💨 Seek shelter, I am very dangerous."}],"options":[{"label":"A Hurricane","isCorrect":false},{"label":"A Tornado","isCorrect":true},{"label":"A Blizzard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌍"}}],"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Moo!' What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I give you milk."},{"text":"🌱 I eat grass."},{"text":"⚫ I have black and white spots."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Woof! Woof!' I like to play fetch. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I love to chew on this."},{"text":"🐾 I have four legs and a tail."},{"text":"🏡 I live in a kennel or house."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Meow!' and like to chase mice. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧶 I like to play with yarn."},{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk."},{"text":"🐈‍⬛ I can be many colors."}],"options":[{"label":"Fish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I quack and swim in a pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦆 I have a flat bill."},{"text":"💦 I love to be in the water."},{"text":"🥚 My babies are called ducklings"}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Chicken","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I oink and roll in the mud. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐷 I'm often pink."},{"text":"🥓 People eat bacon from me"},{"text":"🐽 I have a snout."}],"options":[{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I like to hop and I love carrots. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 My favorite food is orange."},{"text":"🐰 I have long ears."},{"text":"🦘 I jump around."}],"options":[{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Squirrel","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I chirp and fly in the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐦 I lay eggs in a nest."},{"text":"🐛 I eat worms."},{"text":"🦋 I have wings."}],"options":[{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fish","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Turtle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I say 'Neigh!' and people ride on my back. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐴 I wear horseshoes on my feet."},{"text":"🌾 I eat hay."},{"text":"🐎 People say giddy up to make me move!"}],"options":[{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I am the king of the jungle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦁 I have a big mane."},{"text":"🐾 I am a big cat."},{"text":"🥩 I eat meat."}],"options":[{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐘 I can pick things up with my nose."},{"text":"🥜 I like to eat peanuts."},{"text":"🦣 I am big and gray."}],"options":[{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fox","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🌍"}}]}